Welcome to our next section.
By now you should be well versed.
Your brain should be in gear and hopefully your fingers are loose and dexterous because you've been
trying all the HTML coding that we've been learning.
So we now want to take your skills and see if we can put them all together into something cool and fun.
So we've already built our website, which is our fun little thing about education quotes that rock
my world.
But it's time to now take this all together and try something different.
So you know what I was thinking?
Yeah.
How do you know what I was thinking?
Because Google knows.
Google knows.
Google just gives you that feeling sometimes, you know.
Ah, okay.
So I came across something.
What did you come across this?
Uh, I think we both came across it.
This sort of thing.
What have we got here?
What's going on?
So this is basically a website of a whole bunch of recipes, and, um, you can go in and be like,
oh, I made this chocolate cake.
So blackout chocolate cake.
If we go here, we'll see.
They've got, um, an image here that looks good with this cake and it's got a title.
Yeah.
These people that like cake too much.
Um, and then it's got some information on the side.
Um, then it's got some instructions and all the details about the cake.
Okay, so it's basically a relatively simple site.
It's got a whole lot of images and obviously the layout, you can decide how you want it.
But basically I'm looking at this part here.
It's got a whole lot of little images.
And each one of them is a cake that you can click on.
And it's going to show you something.
Okay.
So we'll just focus on trying to make one of these little tab things here.
Yeah.
Well once you've done one I mean it's basically the same thing over and over again.
The same thing.
So then obviously like, you know what we did with our quotes, we've got like all these little images.
So you can see with this, um, like instead of having a quote, they've got whatever chocolate cake
and they've got it all in a table.
You know how we said table, table table.
Uh, row row row row row.
Yeah.
So it's basically a table just like we've done.
So let's see if we can set up something like this, something delicious, something super sweet and
make our own cake website.
So I'm good.
Yeah.
Sounds good.
Okay.
So that's what our plan.
Our plan is for this section.
So I'm sorry about this.
If you're feeling hungry, this is your time.
I'll go out and get yourself a cake and stuff it down your throat.
Because this is going to be hard.
Really hard because we're going to be making your delicious cake website.
So get ready, prepare yourself mentally, physically, emotionally and everything else as we get ready
for a tasty cake experience online.